ultimaterollercoaster.com 2009-06-26

# Ultimate Rollercoaster | Privacy Policy

It is our desire at Ultimate Rollercoaster® to protect the privacy of our guests. This document describes our policy regarding information collected or received during your visit to our web site. Please note that the amount and type of information gathered will vary depending upon your usage.

**Collection of Personal Information**

You can visit the Ultimate Rollercoaster Web site without revealing any personal, identifiable information. The only information collected during a normal visit is your IP address, browser version, type of computer operating system, referring URL (if any) and a record of the content you viewed, along with the date and time of those requests. During normal browsing we do not collect or store information such as your name, mailing address or email address.

This information gathered during this usage may be used to generate reports that measure site usage activity. This information is used to improve the site experience and monitor the activity on our servers. We may also share this information with advertisers and affiliates for information purposes. There are sections or features on the site that will require you to submit personal, identifiable information to obtain access or use these features. The collection, handling and use of this information will be discussed below.

**IP Addresses**

During your visit to Ultimate Rollercoaster we will record your activity by collecting and storing your IP address along with the requests for content from our servers for the purposes of statistics reporting, system administration, and security.

An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're on the Internet. Servers use the assigned IP address to identify your computer.

When you request content from our web servers your IP address is automatically logged. For general use you may remain anonymous to us since our web logs do not contain personal, identifiable information connected and/or linked to your IP address.

There are exceptions to linking personal identifiable information to your IP address. When using our message boards, chat rooms, user profiles, member registration, polls, features that require you to sign in or contacting us by email, then your IP address may be noted and logged along with any personal information you voluntarily or are required to submit. This information may include but is not limited to your name, home address and email address.

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that a web server transfers to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies are harmless and in most cases are used to enhance your online experience by storing your user name, preferences, sessions and other features while using a Web site.

We may also use cookies to help us track site activity, including page views, return visits and feature usage. Many of the improvements to the site are based on data that can be collected through the use of cookies.

Web browsers are generally set to accept cookies by default. If you'd prefer not to accept cookies then you can change the preferences on your browser to not accept cookies or to alert you prior to accepting one.

Ultimate Rollercoaster uses cookies to store preferences, monitor site activity and store session information to enhance your online experience on this web site and to enable features such as our message boards, chat rooms, member registration, member features and polls to function properly. Some sections and site features will not work or function properly without the use of cookies.

Ultimate Rollercoaster does not use cookies to retrieve personal information from your computer that was not originally sent to you from our web servers. We do not use cookies internally for site marketing or promotion, nor is the information we store in our cookies shared with third parties.

Some of our cookies sent and stored on your local computer may contain personal identifiable information such as your name, user name or ID and other information that possibly could be traced to you.

You may receive cookies from our advertisers, affiliates and ad networks. Ultimate Rollercoaster, uses third-parties to server advertising on this web site and has no control over the use of these cookies; therefore they are not subject to our Privacy Policy. The use of cookies by our advertisers is common practice and for more information on how these cookies are used, please read the privacy statements for our advertisers listed below.

**Collection of Personal Identifiable Information**

There are instances or situations on this Web site that may require you to submit personal information to our Web servers. This information such as your name, mailing address, or email address is received, collected and stored on our web servers. Ultimate Rollercoaster is concerned about your privacy and therefore we take measures to ensure that the information we collect is secure from outside sources.

In some cases the personal information you submit, may be accessible to other visitors of this web site. If it is your desire to remain completely anonymous then you should not participate or use features of the site that require you to submit personal information.

Please be aware that whenever you give out personal information online - for example, via chat rooms, discussion forums, message boards or user profiles -- information can be collected and used by people and/or third parties you don't know. While it is our goal to protect our users' privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose for public display, and therefore you do so at your own risk.

**Information Sharing**

Ultimate Rollercoaster follows strict policies to protect your personal information. In general it is our policy not to share personal information with outside sources and third parties, unless our intention to do so is stated up front.

Ultimate Rollercoaster policy is to not sell, trade, rent or otherwise reveal your personal information to third parties, unless consent is given or the intended use is stated at the time of collection, except for the following situations:

1\. to protect the rights, property, and safety of Ultimate Rollercoaster, our owner(s), users, or others;

2\. to enforce or apply our Terms of Service agreement;

3\. to protect the security and integrity of our Web site;

4\. to take precautions against liability;

5\. to respond to judicial process; or

6\. to the extent permitted under other provisions of law, to provide information to law enforcement or for an investigation on matter related to public safety.

In these situations, we reserve the right to release any and all of your personal information if we believe that such release is reasonably necessary.

All users should be aware that personal, identifiable information may be gathered by third parties without our knowledge in our chat rooms, discussion forums, message boards, user profiles and anywhere else where this information is displayed for public consumption. The information in these areas of the site is on public display, therefore we cannot protect or prevent the collection of this information.

Ultimate Rollercoaster may use information gathered from this web site to generate demographic data, which may be shared with third parties. The data shared does not contain personal, identifiable information unless consent was given at the time of collection for such a use.

Should exception to our information sharing policy exist, full disclosure will be made at the time of collection.

**Electronic Mail**

In some situations we may collect and/or store your email address. Ultimate Rollercoaster is concerned about unsolicited email, otherwise known as Spam. Therefore, it is our policy not to sell or share any email address with third parties, unless consent is given or the intended use is clearly stated at the time of collection. However we do reserve the right to use your email address for internal use.

On occasion you may receive email from Ultimate Rollercoaster for informative or promotional purposes. If at any time you wish to be removed from our mailing lists please visit our Contact Us page to send a request through email. Please include the email address to be removed and if applicable a copy of the message you received prompting your request to be removed. We promise to honor your request and remove your email address from any future mailings.

You may also opt ot of receiving electronic messages from Ultimate Rollercoaster.com by contacting us via postal mail. Please send notice, including the e-mail address you are receiving messages from us to:

Ultimate Rollercoaster.com  
1100 Irvine Blvd #440  
Tustin, CA 92782  
714.389-3613

**Advertising**

Ultimate Rollercoaster uses third parties and ad networks for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing-messages on the site. The third parties and ad networks we work with are also serious about your privacy and provide their own privacy policies that may or may not apply to this web site.

For more information on how our third parties handle personal information related to the advertising on this site, please visit the web site for each of the following:

Burst! Media, LLC - To find out more about how Burst! handles your personal information please consult the [Burst! Privacy Statement](http://www.burstmedia.com/isl/index.asp?page=privacy).

ValueClick - To find out more about how ValueClick handles your personal information please consult the [ValueClick Privacy Statement](http://www.valueclick.com/privacy.html).

Tribal Fusion - To find out more about how Tribal Fusion handles your personal information please consult the [Tribal Fusion Privacy Statement](http://www.tribalfusion.com/TribalFusion/privacy.html).

Casale Media - To find out more about how Casale Media handles your personal information please consult the [Casale Media Privacy Statement](http://www.casalemedia.com/privacy.html).

Google AdSense - To find out more about how Google handles your personal information please consult the [Google Privacy Statement](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).

Commission Junction - To find out more about how Commission Junction handles your personal information please consult the [Commission Junction Privacy Statement](http://www.cj.com/privacy.html).

**Hyperlinks**

Ultimate Rollercoaster features hyperlinks to other web sites that are independent of this site. The privacy policy is limited to the content hosted under the ultimaterollercoaster.com domain and does not apply to web sites that we provide links to.

Ultimate Rollercoaster, it's owner(s), webmaster(s), author(s), producer(s) and affiliate(s), make no representation or warranty as to the accuracy, completeness or authenticity of the information contained in any hyperlink or web site that we link to. Please note that hyperlinks are not to be taken as an endorsement by Ultimate Rollercoaster. Use of any hyperlink is done so at your own risk and you willingly accept all risks and liability of doing so.

Please note hyperlinks are not to be taken as an endorsement by Ultimate Rollercoaster. Your linking to any off-site pages or web sites is done at your own risk and you willingly accept the risks and liability of doing so.

**Information Accuracy**

Ultimate Rollercoaster features information on, but not limited to roller coasters, theme parks, thrill rides and amusement parks. The owner(s), webmaster(s), author(s), producer(s) and affiliate(s) of this site reserve the right to modify the information at any time without notice.

Every effort is taken to insure the accuracy of the information presented on this web site, but Ultimate Rollercoaster the owner(s), webmaster(s), author(s), producer(s) and affiliate(s) do not accept responsibility for the accuracy, completeness or authenticity of any of the information contained herein on this web site. This web site and the information presented is provided "as is" without any warranties or guarantees of any kind.

**Limitations of Liability**

Ultimate Rollercoaster reserves the right to modify the Privacy Policy in any manner, at any time, without notice of any kind. The latest copy of this agreement can be read online at <http://www.ultimaterollercoaster.com/info/privacy.html>

Ultimate Rollercoaster can in no way guarantee your confidential use of this web site. The owner(s), webmaster(s), author(s), producer(s) and affiliate(s), shall not be held responsible for any harm that you or any person may suffer as a result of any breach of confidentiality in respect to your use of this site or any personal information you release to this site.

**Questions and Contact Information**

Please Contact Us with any questions you may have regarding this Privacy Policy.
